Guide to the Larry Rivers Papers 1952-2010 MSS 293
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XVI: Video
  - Pablo Ferro's Original Jive Part-One, 1972 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0420)
    Format: VHS
    Pablo Ferro Original Jive
  - Pablo Ferro's Original Jam Part-One, 1972 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0421)
    TRT: [approx. 45 minutes]
  - Montage for "An Evening with Pablo Ferro", 1992 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0422)
    TRT: [approx. 10 minutes]
    An Evening with Pablo Ferro
  - [Pablo Ferro K-NBC-4 Interview], 1999 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0423)
    TRT: [approx. 5 minutes]
    Pablo Ferro
  - [Saturn Awards Historical Sequences by Pablo Ferro], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0424)
    Saturn Awards
  - Unknown, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0425)
    TRT: [approx. 120 minutes]
  - [Unknown, TV Shows], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0426)
  - The Bronx, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0427)
  - PBS Web Spot w/Sam Rivers I, May 1 1998 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0428)
    PBS Web Spot with Sam
  - PBS Web Spot w/Sam Rivers II, May 8 2010 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0429)
  - "When the World Was Over," by Barbara Probst Solomon, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0430)
    When the World Was Over - Barbara Solomon
  - Witness & Legacy, 1995 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0431)
  - Witness & Legacy Wate, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0432)
    Witness & Legacy
  - LTV 8850 What Did I Do?, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0433)
    TRT: 00:48:00
    L.R. What Did I Do?
  - LTV 8850 What Did I Do?, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0434)
  - Sam's Birthday '90, 1990 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0435)
    Sam's Birthday
  - [TV Shows], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0436)
  - [Aunt Denny & Family], 1984 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0437)
    Aunt Denny Family 1984
  - [EHS Talent Show 2000], Apr 16 2000 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0438)
    EHS Talent Show
  - [Shirley I], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0439)
  - [Shirley II], Jul 17 1983 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0440)
    TRT: 00:45:31
  - [Shirley III], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0441)
    TRT: 00:60:00
  - Scoop Evelyn Waugh, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0442)
    TRT: 02:00:00
  - [Modern American Poets: Frank O'Hara], Apr 24 1996 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0443)
    Frank O'Hara
  - [Beats at the Whitney, City Arts], Nov 2 1995 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0444)
    Beat Show Interview
  - Larry Rivers Playing with Phoebe Legere At Bobby Vans, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0445)
  - [Climax Band?], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0446)
    Climax Band Continental Divide
  - [Music Express, Palm Beach Airport], Dec 18 1991 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0447)
    Music Express Palm Beach
  - Enema, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0448)
    TRT: [approx. 90 minutes]
  - [Phoebe I], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0449)
    Phoebe
  - [Phoebe II], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0450)
  - [Kenny Mack], undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0451)
    Kenny Mack Very Special Arts
  - Fashion TV: Robert Rauschenberg & Chuck Close, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0452)
  - Niki De Saint Phalle Portrait, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0453)
    Niki De Saint-Phalle
  - L.R. Band, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0454)
    TRT: [approx. 160 minutes]
  - [Cloud House Poetry Archive, Larry Rivers & Arnold Weinstein], Oct 29 1992 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0455)
    L.R. & Arnold W. Cloudhouse Poetry
  - Tits, undated (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0456)
    TRT: 00:53:00
    L.R. Tits
  - In the Studio with Larry Rivers, Part #1 & #2, Oct 1982 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0457)
    In the Studio with L.R.
  - James Rosenquist: A Film By Edwin Leiser, 1986 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0458)
    James Rosenquist
  - America, 1930-1970: 40 Anni D'arte, Societa, Costume, 1992 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0459)
    TRT: 00:45:00
    America 1930 - 1970
  - Something Wonderful May Happen, 2001 (Box 125, Media ID: 293.0460)
    TRT: 00:56:00
  - The Anatomy of Cindy Fink, 20 Aug 1993 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0461)
    TRT: 00:11:45
    Anatomy of Cindy Fink - Barbara Solomon
  - Larry Rivers Interview at 404, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0462)
    TRT: 00:15:00
    L.R. Interview at 404
  - History of the Jews Parts I & II, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0463)
    History of the Jews I, II - Channel 13
  - History of the Jews Part III, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0464)
    History of the Jews III - Channel 13
  - Zihuatanejo - Places & Faces, Feb 1994 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0465)
  - Fashion TV - L.R., Jun 29 2000 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0466)
  - Art Students League of New York: Larry Rivers, 10 Feb 1998 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0467)
    Art Students League L.R.
  - [Larry Rivers Interview "Retrospective"], 1990 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0468)
    TRT: 01:34:00
    L.R. Interview 1990
  - Painting With Light, Apr 28 1990 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0469)
    Painting with Light L.R.
  - Larry Rivers: Every Picture Tells a Story, Dec 10 1990 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0470)
    TRT: 00:30:00
  - [Arabella Pollen Autumn/Winter Collection 1992] (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0471)
    Arabella Pollen
  - [Helen Storey Autumn/Winter Collection 1992] (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0472)
    Helen Storey
  - Jodi Head Fashions, 1992 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0473)
  - Jodi Head Fashions, 1992 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0474)
  - [Ghost Autumn/Winter Collection 1992] (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0475)
    Ghost
  - [Fernando Sanchez Ltd Spring 1993] (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0476)
    Fernando Sanchez 2
  - Unknown, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0477)
  - [The War Room: A Work in Progress], 1992 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0478)
    The War Room
  - [Scenes - from a Work in Progress, The War Room], 1992 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0479)
  - Fashion Televsion - Larry Rivers, Jul 29 2000 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0480)
    Fashion TV L.R.
  - [Sideshow of the Absurd I], undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0481)
    TRT: 00:05:00
    Pam Joseph Sideshow of the Absurd
  - [Sideshow of the Absurd II], undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0482)
    TRT: 00:08:30
  - [Sideshow of the Absurd III], undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0483)
    TRT: 00:09:00
  - "Art in Moscow" Promo, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0484)
    TRT: 00:07:00
    Art in Moscow
  - Deb and Michael McKenzie, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0485)
  - [Phoebe Legere], undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0486)
  - Africa and I/Round Trip, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0487)
    TRT: 01:02:00
    Africa & I Pierre Gaisseau
  - Larry Rivers: Public and Private, Jun 5 2002 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0488)
    TRT: 01:29:59
  - Larry Rivers: Public and Private, Jun 5 2002 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0489)
  - Larry Rivers: Public and Private, Jun 5 2002 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0490)
  - Larry Rivers: Public and Private, Jun 5 2002 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0491)
  - Larry Rivers: An American Master, 1993 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0492)
    TRT: 00:28:00
  - Larry Rivers: An American Master, 1993 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0493)
  - Larry Rivers: An American Master, 1993 (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0494)
  - California Trip, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0495)
  - Paradise - Niki & Jean, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0496)
    Paradise
  - 747 to Stockholm, undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0497)
  - [Stockholm, Opening, Visit to Palace], undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0498)
    Stockholm
  - [Swedish Museum, American Collection], undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0499)
    Swedish Museum
  - Stockholm Show (copy), undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0500)
    Stockholm Show
  - [Washington I original], undated (Box 126, Media ID: 293.0501)
  - [Washington II original], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0502)
    Washington
  - [Washington edited], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0503)
  - Peekskill Wedding I, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0504)
    Peekskill Wedding
  - [Peekskill Wedding II and P.R. street fiesta], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0505)
  - Florida - Everglades, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0506)
  - Florida - Disneyworld, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0507)
  - Florida - Seminole Village, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0508)
  - Florida I, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0509)
  - Florida II - Speeding Ticket, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0510)
  - Puerto Rico, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0511)
  - Haiti I, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0512)
    Haiti
  - Haiti - Leaving, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0513)
  - Haiti Voodoo I, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0514)
  - Haiti Voodoo II, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0515)
  - Haiti - Bar Royale, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0516)
  - Africa - Peter Beard's Backyard, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0517)
  - [Africa - Jackals, Carcass, Street Scenes], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0518)
    Africa 13
  - [Africa Practice Edits], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0519)
  - [Africa - Nairobi in Car], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0520)
    Africa 14
  - [Africa - Ndutu Safari/Peter], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0521)
    Africa 1
  - Africa - Ndutu, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0522)
    Africa Ndutu
  - Africa - Manyara, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0523)
    Africa Manyara
  - [Africa - Manyara/Ians Camp/Animals/Aureo Interview], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0524)
    Africa 4
  - Africa - Humans on the Rock, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0525)
    Africa 5
  - Africa - Manyara, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0526)
    Africa 6
  - Africa 7, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0527)
  - Africa 8, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0528)
  - Africa - Ndutu, the Camp, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0529)
    Africa 9
  - [Africa - Ndutu/Wildebeest/Hyena/Vultures], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0530)
    Africa 10
  - [Africa - Ndutu interview/Masai boys], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0531)
    Africa 11
  - Africa - Barbara Practice Video, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0532)
    Africa 12
  - Africa - Happy Birthday Peter, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0533)
    Africa 15
  - Peter Beard Press Conference, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0534)
  - Peter Beard Press Conference, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0535)
  - Peter Beard's Show, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0536)
  - Russia - Visit to Yuri & Igor, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0537)
    Russia Yuri & Igor
  - Russia - Samarkand, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0538)
    Russia Samar Kand
  - Russia - Leningrad, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0539)
    Russia Lenin Grd
  - Russia - Moscow I and Leningrad, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0540)
    Russia Moscow I
  - Russia Tulins Studio, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0541)
  - Russia - Museum, Hotel Bedroom, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0542)
  - Russia Tashkent, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0543)
  - Russia Bukhara, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0544)
  - Russia - Red Square, Kremlin, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0545)
  - Abbie Kiss & Tell, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0546)
  - Abs Vas II, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0547)
  - Abs Vas III, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0548)
  - [Abs Vas - operation], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0549)
    Abs Vas 6
  - [Abs Vas #7], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0550)
    Abs Vas 7
  - [Abs Vas - WBAI], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0551)
    Abs Vas 9
  - Abs Vas 2nd interview, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0552)
  - [Abs Vas - Abbie & 2nd child, 1st marriage, 1st visit to doctor, car to N.Y.], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0553)
  - [Abs Vas - Dr. Davis' Office], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0554)
    Abs Vas Dr. Davis
  - Abs Vas - Abs Adventure, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0555)
  - Abbie Hoffman, Ch. 13, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0556)
  - Abbie Hoffman - T.V.T.V. interview, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0557)
  - Diana Pool, undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0558)
  - [N.G.T.F. Luis Cruz, Jesuit Priest], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0559)
  - [N.G.T.F. Luis Cruz cont. Margo St. James], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0560)
  - [N.G.T.F. Margo St. James], undated (Box 127, Media ID: 293.0561)
    Margo St. James
  - [N.G.T.F. Meeting, Marilyn Haft of ACLU], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0562)
    N.G.T.F. Meeting
  - David Goodstein Advocate, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0563)
  - David Goodstein Advocate, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0564)
  - B.B. Painting, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0565)
  - [B.B. Intro and Titles], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0566)
  - B.B. Painting I, Nov 12 1975 (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0567)
  - B.B. Painting II, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0568)
  - B.B. Painting III, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0569)
  - B.B. Painting IV, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0570)
  - B.B. Painting V, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0571)
  - B.B. Painting VI, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0572)
  - B.B. Painting VII, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0573)
  - B.B. Painting Last, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0574)
  - Painting Beauty and the Beast, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0575)
  - [B.B. edited (copy A)], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0576)
    B.B. Edited
  - [B.B. edited (copy)], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0577)
  - [Beauty + the Beast paintings], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0578)
  - Packaged Beauty I, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0579)
  - Packaged Beauty II, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0580)
  - [Packaged Beauty III], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0581)
  - Packaged Beauty IV, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0582)
  - [Packaged Beauty 1st edit], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0583)
  - [Packaged Beauty Final], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0584)
  - [Packaged Beauty Final], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0585)
  - [Packaged Beauty "the Package"], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0586)
  - [Packaged Beauty T.V. Comm. Book], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0587)
  - Shirley I, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0588)
  - Shirley II, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0589)
  - [Shirley, Kitchen, Arab-Isr. War, T.V. '73], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0590)
    Shirley 12
  - Shirley 5, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0591)
  - My Mother Shirley, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0592)
  - [Shirley, conversation w/Shirley, Enema II], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0593)
    Shirley Enema II
  - [Shirley at Grave, Lydis Ave], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0594)
  - [Shirley, Yom Kippur, Dinner at Garrys], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0595)
    Shirley 11
  - [Shirley shopping], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0596)
    Shirley 10
  - [Shirley - old age, sex], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0597)
    Shirley Old Age
  - [Shirley, burial snd. mix and edited visuals], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0598)
  - [Shirley, Burial, original], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0599)
  - Shirley 14, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0600)
  - Shirley, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0601)
    [Shirley]
  - [Shirley, burial music, titles, not used], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0602)
    Shirley Burial Music
  - [Shirley, Arab-Isr. war, Valeri Singing, Work Reel], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0603)
    Shirley Work Reel
  - [Shirley, mirror, hallway 9], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0604)
    Shirley 9
  - Shirley, Edited Stills I, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0605)
  - [Shirley 4, cousin Leena at Shirleys house], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0606)
    Shirley 4
  - Unknown, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0607)
  - [Peter Beard's Backyard, front titles], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0608)
  - Smell, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0609)
  - [Smell I & II, Larry - Earl - Bessie], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0610)
  - [Smell, Peter Beard's House, Montauk], Sep 6 1975 (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0611)
  - [Smell Cheese shop, Bea Danziger reading], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0612)
  - Smell, undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0613)
  - [Smell Final Edit], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0614)
  - [J.D. on L.R.], undated (Box 128, Media ID: 293.0615)
  - Shirley 18, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0616)
  - Shirley 16, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0617)
  - [Shirley, my mother 1st part], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0618)
    Shirley 27
  - Shirley Edited Stills II, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0619)
  - [Shirley (shot), "Charles, I'm Gay"...George massage], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0620)
  - Shirley Titles, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0621)
  - Shirley 15, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0622)
  - Shirley Work Reel, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0623)
  - [Shirley 13, couch conversation], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0624)
    Shirley 13
  - Smell Toast, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0625)
  - Smell III, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0626)
  - [Ahmet's Birthday, Meet the Turk], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0627)
    Ahmet's Birthday
  - [Ahmet's Birthday Greeting], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0628)
  - [Ahmet's Birthday, Francois-Rainer], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0629)
  - [Ahmet's Birthday Greetings, final], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0630)
  - [Big B Colorized], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0631)
  - [Big B, Edited from 1"], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0632)
  - Jim Carroll, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0633)
  - Hurricane I, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0634)
  - Hurricane II, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0635)
  - Hurricane III, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0636)
  - Delbert & Glenn I, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0637)
  - Delbert & Glenn II, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0638)
  - [Delbert & Glenn - trip to San Diego], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0639)
    Delbert & Glenn
  - [Delbert & Glenn - S.D., L.A., L.A. Backstage], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0640)
  - [Delbert & Glenn, backstage], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0641)
  - [Delbert & Glenn, Big Al Go-Go], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0642)
  - [Delbert & Glenn, Big Als Last Tape], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0643)
  - [Woman Is Fickle, La Donne Mobile (fin vers.)], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0644)
  - [Woman is Fickle, La Donne Mobile, fin. vers.], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0645)
  - [Woman is Fickle, Katie & Kid, Africa (Map) P.B. Backyard], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0646)
  - [La Done ay Mub eelay Titles], Jul 4 1973 (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0647)
  - [La Donne Mob el Lay final version], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0648)
  - [La Donne Mobile Peter Beard - Barbara Allen], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0649)
  - [La Donna Mob elay, Woman is Fickle], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0650)
  - [Twig 1, California: Diana-Earl], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0651)
  - Twig 14st, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0652)
  - Twig II, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0653)
    [Twig]
  - [Twig II Algonqiun], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0654)
    Twig II
  - [Twig I & II edited], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0655)
    Twig I & II
  - [Village Idiot - French Reel II], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0656)
  - [Edited splits, crime special for Village Idiot], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0657)
  - [Doing the Village Idiot], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0658)
  - [Village Idiot Bath Scene], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0659)
  - [Village Idiot French Reel], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0660)
  - [Splits orig.], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0661)
    Splits
  - [Tattoo Titles - Shinnecock Pow-wow], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0662)
    Tattoo Titles
  - [Dianas Tattoo 1], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0663)
    Diana's Tattoo
  - [Dianas Tattoo 2], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0664)
  - Tattoo Party I, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0665)
  - Tattoo Party II, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0666)
  - American Couple I, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0667)
  - [American Couple II edited Katy II], undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0668)
    American Couple II
  - American Couples Joe + Allan, undated (Box 129, Media ID: 293.0669)
  - American Couples Ciccone, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0670)
  - American Couples Ciccone II, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0671)
  - [American Couples Tamara Ciccone - Pablo, Katherine], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0672)
  - [Edited Couples I Katy close-up], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0673)
    Edited Couples I
  - [American Couples II Katy], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0674)
  - Amelio I, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0675)
  - Amelio II, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0676)
  - [The Artist II edited version], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0677)
    The Artist II
  - Artist Dedication, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0678)
  - [The Artist, Pacific Ocean], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0679)
  - The Artist 6, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0680)
  - [Artist], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0681)
  - The Artist, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0682)
  - [The Artist, summer diary writing, cleve, cherrywood, Ava II], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0683)
  - [The Artist, cherrywood, steel cigars], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0684)
  - K. Koch, the Artist I, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0685)
  - K. Koch, the Artist II, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0686)
  - Strange Test Daria, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0687)
  - [Dorothy Miller 2, Cahills Wife], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0688)
    Dorothy Miller
  - Barney Montage, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0689)
  - [WPA copy from 3/4], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0690)
  - Painting Beauty and the Beasts, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0691)
  - Twig, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0692)
  - The Last Rally, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0693)
  - L.R. Dick Cavett, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0694)
  - Sonya I, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0695)
  - Sonya II, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0696)
  - 3 Octogenarians, 4 Aug 1975 (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0697)
  - Mama's Baking Lesson, Aug 3-4 1975 (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0698)
  - Hampton Vaudeville I, 1972 (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0699)
  - Hampton Vaudeville II, 1972 (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0700)
  - [Hampton Vaudeville McGovern practice], 1972 (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0701)
  - Hampton Vaudeville IV, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0702)
  - Nature Video, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0703)
  - Panel Bridgehampton Zoo, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0704)
  - [AAGE Accident], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0705)
  - Shark I, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0706)
  - Shark II, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0707)
  - Shark III, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0708)
  - Accident on Little Plains Rd, Jul 10 1976 (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0709)
  - Hitchers, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0710)
  - 3 Girls Mel Climbing, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0711)
    TRT: [approx. 180 minutes]
  - Gino Piano, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0712)
  - [Last Mango, Village Idiot, Partially edited], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0713)
  - K. Koch T. Southern, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0714)
  - Zoo Bridgehampton, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0715)
  - Brigids Fish Dinner, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0716)
  - Christ Pageant 74, 1974 (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0717)
  - 100 miles to N.Y. I, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0718)
  - Judy & David Party, undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0719)
  - July 4th 1973 I, Jul 4 1973 (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0720)
  - [July 4th 1973 IIa], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0721)
    July 4th 1973
  - [July 4th 1973 IIb], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0722)
  - [Augusta at Studio], undated (Box 130, Media ID: 293.0723)
  - 100 Miles to N.Y. II, undated (Box 131, Media ID: 293.0724)
  - Bob Collacello's Parents, undated (Box 131, Media ID: 293.0725)
  - July 4th 1975 I, Jul 4 1975 (Box 131, Media ID: 293.0726)
    July 4th 1975
  - July 4th 1975 II, Jul 4 1975 (Box 131, Media ID: 293.0727)
  - July 5th 1976 I, Jul 5 1976 (Box 131, Media ID: 293.0728)
    July 5th 1976
  - July 5th 1976 II, Jul 5 1976 (Box 131, Media ID: 293.0729)
  - Brigids Cake Mix, undated (Box 131, Media ID: 293.0730)
  - [Jerome's Farewell, Pool], undated (Box 131, Media ID: 293.0731)